<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sergey Rodin</title>
    <link>https://www.sergeyrodin.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sergey Rodin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 12:28:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sergeyrodin.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.sergeyrodin.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sergeyrodin.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Sergey. I&amp;rsquo;m a software technical writer with 10 years of experience in the logistics and Web3 industries.
From 2015 to 2023, I worked as a technical writer in the logistics industry in Southeast Asia, focusing on internal and external documentation and processes.
In 2023, I joined Sky Mavis, a Web3 gaming startup behind the popular Axie Infinity game and the Ronin blockchain. At Sky Mavis, I write and proofread content for developers and end users, design the information architecture and maintain the underlying infrastructure of the documentation websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact information</title>
      <link>https://www.sergeyrodin.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sergeyrodin.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Email: contact@sergeyrodin.com Telegram: @golodinsky Phone number: +84702963470 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://www.sergeyrodin.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sergeyrodin.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>Profile Experienced technical writer with over 10 years of expertise creating documentation for end users and developers, including guides, APIs, and SDKs. Proficient in Docs-as-Code methodology, git, and command line. Skilled in researching and writing effective technical documentation for engineers. Demonstrated success in leading large- scale documentation efforts, launching developer portals and end-user documentation sites. Proven track record of maintaining consistency and quality across multiple documentation sets by adhering to style guides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing samples</title>
      <link>https://www.sergeyrodin.com/samples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sergeyrodin.com/samples/</guid>
      <description>This page contains my selected writing samples.
Sky Mavis documentation Ronin blockchain documentation: docs.roninchain.com Sky Mavis developer documentation: docs.skymavis.com Tutorial Create a shipper (fragment)
This is a fragment of a tutorial that explains how to create a shipper in a system used by the operations team. The PDF was exported from a Confluence page, where the entire tutorial is published.
API integration guide Order API integration guide (fragment)
This is a fragment of an integration guide for a logistics API used to create delivery orders.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
